all right going off the last one
government watchdogs that we need to be
so that was kind of more of the EPA this
also I think we need to take back the
FDA and I don't know what the caning
quick montage that's happened but the
federal drug administered to where we
trust the government we assume that if
it's on our shelves it's safe this goes
back to the product app but making sure
that we know I don't think people
realize how much testing is not done
that a lot of times not as so much in
food but in other things we put into our
environment that from what I know
companies are allowed to just make it
until it's proven to be problematic as
opposed to in the opposite way where you
have to prove that it's benign before
you can put it into the environment and
create it so just having that
information just about the FDA so the
actual things that are more regulated
find you know what has been seen to be
safe is aspartame safe how do we know
that not we take the FDA stamp of
approval but like what tests were done
who paid for those tests what did those
tests say what tests have been done
further on it should it be okay what
countries have allowed it what countries
haven't allowed it what's their
reasoning and seeing okay the same thing
for every single chemical and additive I
mean maybe it can be done for things
like salt and baking soda that are
natural as well but a finding out what
is safe and what's not I mean I don't
know if there's been any studies that
show salt itself is it's been done
studies in salt what am I talking about
and shown just like sodium itself being
able to see more so what the ingredients
that MSG is it safe is it safe for
everyone is a safer certain amount of
people just being able to tell what
process was gone through to show that
it's safe so you can say yep the
government did their due diligence or
they didn't and we need more further
study I think that is an important
aspect of our lives we need to take back
immediately from our governor
that was a couple number eight